<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<title>Scramble the Duck’s Official Website</title>
	<subtitle>Scramble is completely accurate weather-predicting duck in Eastford, Connecticut.</subtitle>
	<link href="https://scrambletheduck.org/feed.xml" rel="self"/>
	<link href="https://scrambletheduck.org"/>
	<updated>2022-01-27T15:43:14-05:00</updated>
	<id>https://scrambletheduck.org/</id>
	<author>
		<name>The Duck Handlers</name>
	</author>
	
	<entry>
		<title>Scramble the Duck to Predict Spring or Winter</title>
		<link href="https://scrambletheduck.org/news/2022/01/27/2022-1-24-scramble-the-duck-to-predict-spring-or-winter/"/>
		<updated>2022-01-27T15:43:14-05:00</updated>
		<id>https://scrambletheduck.org/news/2022/01/27/2022-1-24-scramble-the-duck-to-predict-spring-or-winter/</id>
		<content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Scramble the Duck, the accurate weather-predicting groundhog alternative, will predict an early spring or six more weeks of winter. The event will be held on February 2, 7:30 a.m. at the Ivy Glenn Memorial in Eastford. The event will also be livestreamed on Scramble the Duck’s website.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With the passing of his late predecessor, Scramble the Duck, Sr., Scramble the Duck, Jr. will predict the weather this year. He boasts similar credentials, having graduated from Stormy Heights Academy with a “Ducktorate” in weather prognostication.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;People are invited to the event in person at the Ivy Glenn Memorial. The event will also be livestreamed at &lt;a href=&quot;https://scrambletheduck.org/livestream&quot;&gt;scrambletheduck.org/livestream&lt;/a&gt;. Fans are encouraged to celebrate online if they are not able to attend the event.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
	</entry>
	
	
	<entry>
		<title>Announcing the Passing of Scramble the Duck</title>
		<link href="https://scrambletheduck.org/news/2021/12/02/announcing-the-passing-of-scramble-the-duck/"/>
		<updated>2021-12-02T00:00:00-05:00</updated>
		<id>https://scrambletheduck.org/news/2021/12/02/announcing-the-passing-of-scramble-the-duck/</id>
		<content type="html">&lt;p&gt;It is with sadness that we announce the passing of Scramble after 7 wonderful years. (7 years old is old for a duck.) We are forever grateful for his help in predicting the weather in Eastford and the cheer he brought to many.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Scramble helped establish the paramount weather predicting standard that has no rivals, all of which has become Stormy Heights Academy&#39;s curriculum. Through his work weather forecasting has become much more accurate.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Because the job of Eastford weather predictor is a strenuous job requiring great training, we are currently interviewing possible candidates for the job, which will be followed by a rigorous education and training. (Scramble gave us the instructions on how to go about this.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Duck Day will continue, and further announcements will follow. Scramble appreciated everyone who has helped make Duck Day truly ducky.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Scramble served all of us well. We are grateful for everything he provided to us and to the town of Eastford.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
	</entry>
	
	
	<entry>
		<title>Scramble the Duck’s Winter Prediction Proved Accurate</title>
		<link href="https://scrambletheduck.org/news/2021/03/16/scramble-the-ducks-winter-prediction-proved-accurate/"/>
		<updated>2021-03-16T00:00:00-04:00</updated>
		<id>https://scrambletheduck.org/news/2021/03/16/scramble-the-ducks-winter-prediction-proved-accurate/</id>
		<content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Today, at the end of Scramble’s winter prediction, the remaining cold weather shows Scramble’s accuracy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Scramble the Duck, on February 2, 2021, predicted six more weeks of wintery weather. The following blizzards and cold temperatures quickly proved again Scramble’s never-disproven intelligence. The scientific community, once again, stands amazed at Scramble’s infallible grasp of the arts of science.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In a statement to his team, Scramble said,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am glad to provide certainty in my prediction after a very uncertain year. I have no ability to change weather, but I am always glad to inform my fellow New Englanders of the coming weather. Uncertainty creates the greatest anxiety, and after an uncertain year, the weather was no place for further uncertainty. I am glad to help in a small way in this cause, and I encourage everyone to do the same.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Scramble has made seven predictions and has always been &lt;a href=&quot;https://scrambletheduck.org/accuracy/&quot;&gt;accurate.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
	</entry>
	
	
	<entry>
		<title>Scramble forecasts Six More Weeks of Winter</title>
		<link href="https://scrambletheduck.org/news/2021/02/02/scramble-forecasts-more-winter/"/>
		<updated>2021-02-02T00:00:00-05:00</updated>
		<id>https://scrambletheduck.org/news/2021/02/02/scramble-forecasts-more-winter/</id>
		<content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Today, at 7:30 a.m., Scramble the Duck predicted six more weeks of winter.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After the &lt;a href=&quot;https://scrambletheduck.org/speeches/2021/opening/&quot;&gt;opening speech&lt;/a&gt; was read, the doors of the model Ivy Glenn were opened, and Scramble waddled down the red carpet.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://scrambletheduck.org/assets/images/dsc_0103.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;Scramble makes his prediction&quot; loading=&quot;lazy&quot; srcset=&quot;https://scrambletheduck.org/assets/images/dsc_0103-w200.jpeg 200w, https://scrambletheduck.org/assets/images/dsc_0103-w300.jpeg 300w, https://scrambletheduck.org/assets/images/dsc_0103-w600.jpeg 600w, https://scrambletheduck.org/assets/images/dsc_0103-w800.jpeg 800w, https://scrambletheduck.org/assets/images/dsc_0103-w1000.jpeg 1000w&quot; sizes=&quot;(max-width: 60rem) 100vw, 66vw&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Photo by Adam Minor&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Immediately after, Scramble looked for his shadow, and then told his handlers which scroll to read. The &lt;a href=&quot;https://scrambletheduck.org/speeches/2021/announcement/&quot;&gt;prediction announcement&lt;/a&gt; told that Scramble had seen a shadow, forecasting six more weeks of winter. Scramble has made seven predictions, and &lt;a href=&quot;https://scrambletheduck.org/accuracy/&quot;&gt;has a perfect record of accuracy.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://scrambletheduck.org/assets/images/img_7928.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;Scramble&#39;s prediction announcement is read&quot; loading=&quot;lazy&quot; srcset=&quot;https://scrambletheduck.org/assets/images/img_7928-w200.jpeg 200w, https://scrambletheduck.org/assets/images/img_7928-w300.jpeg 300w, https://scrambletheduck.org/assets/images/img_7928-w600.jpeg 600w, https://scrambletheduck.org/assets/images/img_7928-w800.jpeg 800w, https://scrambletheduck.org/assets/images/img_7928-w1000.jpeg 1000w&quot; sizes=&quot;(max-width: 60rem) 100vw, 66vw&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Photo by Paul Torcellini&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;lite-youtube videoid=&quot;RUw8lx2Flrk&quot; style=&quot;background-image: url(&#39;https://i.ytimg.com/vi/RUw8lx2Flrk/hqdefault.jpg&#39;);&quot; class=&quot;undefined&quot; title=&quot;Duck Day 2021&quot;&gt;
    &lt;a class=&quot;lty-playbtn&quot; href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=RUw8lx2Flrk&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot; aria-label=&quot;Play Video (opens in new Tab)&quot; title=&quot;Play Video (opens in new tab)&quot;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;/lite-youtube&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://scrambletheduck.org/press/&quot;&gt;Press resources are available here.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
	</entry>
	
	
	<entry>
		<title>Scramble Featured on WILI Radio</title>
		<link href="https://scrambletheduck.org/news/2021/01/28/scramble-featured-on-wili-am/"/>
		<updated>2021-01-28T00:00:00-05:00</updated>
		<id>https://scrambletheduck.org/news/2021/01/28/scramble-featured-on-wili-am/</id>
		<content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Today, Scramble the Duck was featured on the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.wili.com/&quot;&gt;WILI 1400AM and 95.3FM&lt;/a&gt; Morning Show, interviewed by Wayne Norman.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mixcloud.com/wili1400/12821-scramble-the-ducks-forecast-of-spring/&quot;&gt;You can listen to the interview here.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!--endexcerpt--&gt;
</content>
	</entry>
	
</feed>